Support for NPR comes from Moises, the
creative suite for musicians used by
over 75 million artists worldwide to
learn, create, and collaborate.
Available for phone, tablet, and
desktop. 1 2 3 4 [music]
[music]
>> [music]
>> I'll [singing] love an incurable mask
cuz I like to tidy up.
No blames [music]
and explain it away. They [singing] are
born from my cup.
Rebounds [music and singing] always
running me down like a lion on the
plains.
But this fate [music] is its own escape.
[singing] So I I just stand in place.
And now [music] I find I'm waking up at
sunrise and just lying in bed. Giving
myself a pep [music] talk to survive the
daylight ahead.
>> [music]
>> My past is whiskey glass dipping down a
trunker's [music and singing] throat.
I can't claim I was ever ashamed
[music and singing] when I drank the
antidote.
And now I find [music] I'm waking up the
sunrise and just [music and singing]
lying in bed. Giving myself
a pep talk to survive the day lying
ahead.
But they make they make no difference
when all of the colors blend into black.
[music]
And if I raise [singing] the stakes and
step out out on a ledge, you got to pull
me back
[music]
cuz they make they [singing] make no
difference. Feeling [music] the levy
starting to crack. And if I
[music and singing] raise the stakes and
step out out on the ledge, I'm never
coming [music and singing] back. And
they may they make no
[music and singing] difference. All of
the colors blend into black. [singing]
If I raise the stakes and step out out
on the ledge, you got to pull me back.
[music]
You got a point.
[applause and cheering]
>> [applause]
>> Are you good?
>> Good.
>> Okay. Good.
>> One, two, three, four.
[music]
In my mind. And there's a fog
San Francisco [music]
couldn't handle.
So how this year has been [singing] a
slo
melting both ends of the [music] candle.
And how I wish I could claim
that I don't harbor ill feelings [music]
as my anger's turning to shame.
I [music] stare a hole to the ceiling.
I'm trying to hold it together.
Trying to sleep through the night.
[music] I've got my windows [singing]
open to the weather
and [music] I keep telling my friends
I'm all right.
Yeah, I'm trying to [singing] hold it
together.
I'm trying [music] to [singing] take the
first step
into the arms [music] of wherever
whenever
every [music] day I awake
like a stone over water,
skipping across [music and singing] a
lake
before I sing to the bottom.
But how I wish I [music and singing]
could say
that I'm immune to the mirror
with temples [music] fading to gray.
I'm seeing the end drawing nearer.
[music]
And I could scream and shout
or learn to [music] live without.
But I'm trying [singing]
to hold it together.
[music]
I'm trying to sleep through the night.
I've got my [singing] windows open to
the weather.
I [music] keep telling my friends I'm
all right.
Yeah, I'm trying [music and singing] to
hold it together.
Trying [music]
to take the first step
into the arms wherever,
whenever.
Heat. Heat.
[music]
>> [music]
[applause]
>> Thanks.
[music]
>> [applause]
>> I'm playing an oldie now. They're kind
of a lot of them are becoming oldies
now.
Starting to realize that some of our our
early records came out a similar
distance away from like the Beatles
records when I was a kid.
>> You stop that right now, Ben. Oh,
>> well, that's how time works, Dave.
All right.
[music]
The club compartment
is inacurately [music and singing]
names
and everybody [singing] knows it.
[music]
So I'm proposing [singing]
a swift orderly [music] change
behind its door. There's nothing to keep
my fingers warm. [music]
And all I find are souvenirs [singing]
from better times before the gleam of
your [music] tail lights fading
[singing] east
to find
yourself a [music and singing] better
light.
[music]
>> [music]
>> I was searching
for some legal [music and singing]
documents
as a rain [music]
down on the hood when I stumbled
[singing] upon
pictures I tried to forget.
[music and singing]
And that's how [music] this idea
was drilled [singing] into my head
cuz it's too [music] important
to stay the way it's been.
[music and singing]
But there's no blame for [music] how our
love did slowly [singing] fade. Now that
it's gone, it's [music] like it wasn't
there at all. From here I [music] rest
for disappointment
and regret [singing]
collide. [music]
Flying awake tonight.
There's no [music] blame for how our
love did slowly fade. Now that it's
gone, it's like it [music] wasn't fair
[singing] at all. Here I rest. Where
disappointment [music]
[singing] and regret
collide
[music]
lying awake tonight.
All night [music] when I'm lying awake
tonight.
>> [applause]
[cheering]
>> Thanks.
Thank you. [applause]
Uh we have one more for you. It's a it's
a napalm death cover.
It's very short. [snorts] It was the
only one we could really figure out
because those songs are pretty
complicated. Uh, no, it's one of ours.
Uh, thank you very much for coming. Uh,
I was going to say this evening, but
it's not this evening. Thanks for coming
this morning. I'm programmed to say this
evening because we're on tour, but
thanks for coming. Say h thanks for
watching us.
I want to live
where [music]
sun
and [music] let the sun wrap its arms
[singing]
around me and bathe my skin in water.
[music]
Cool and cleansing and feel
what it's [music] like to be new. Cuz in
my head there's [music] a great
station.
I [music] send my thoughts
to far off destinations
so they may have a chance
of finding [music]
a place where their farm
>> [music and singing]
>> All should
pa
P.
[music and singing]
[music]
I [music] cannot guess
what we'll [singing]
discover [music]
when we turn the [singing] dirt with our
[music] palms cup like shovels. But I
know our filthy hands
can wash one another.
[music]
Not one speck will [music] I do believe
it's true. But there are roses left in
both of our shoes. [music] But if the
silence takes you, then I hope [singing]
it takes me too.
So please I'll hold you near [music] cuz
you're the only song I want to hear.
[singing] A melody softly [music]
soaring through my atmosphere.
Where's each spot?
Where's
[music] SP?
Where are
SP?
[music] I do believe it's true that
there are roads left in both of our
shoes. But if the [music] silence takes
you, then I [singing] hope it takes me
too. [music]
So brown eyes, I'll hold you here.
[music and singing]
Cuz you're the only song I want to hear.
A melody softly [music]
soaring through my atmosphere.
A melody [music]
softly soaring through my atmosphere.
A meloy [music] softly soaring through
my atmosphere.
A melody [music and singing] softly
soaring through my atmosphere.
[cheering and applause]
[applause and cheering]
[applause]
>> [cheering]
[cheering]
[applause]
[applause and cheering]
>> Thanks so much for watching. Support for
NPR music comes from Moises, committed
to ethical innovation and empowering the
creative community with tools for
musicians to master their craft.
A quick update before you go, we're
doing another Tiny Desk giveaway. Enter
by September 12th, 2026, and you and a
friend could win a free trip to DC to
see a Tiny Desk concert live [music] in
person. You even get to choose which
upcoming show you want to see, and it's
completely free to enter. Just go to
npr.org/tinyes
giveaway. Entering is completely free,
but you can get more entries by snagging
some limited edition Tiny Desk merch or
by making a special donation to the NPR
network. Learn more and enter today at
npr.org/tinyes
giveaway.